https://terapatrick.com/pages.php?id=privacy

Privacy Policy
Effective as of January 1, 2009 (the "Effective Date")
TeraPatrick values your privacy and the information we collect. This Policy explains what information terapatrick.com (the Site) collects about you and what we do with it. This Privacy Policy may be revised, changed, altered or updated from time to time without notice by terapatrick, in terapatrick sole discretion. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will always be located and displayed on the Site with the new Effective Date at the top. We may also use alternative methods to alert you to changes to the Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. By using or navigating the Site, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use or visit terapatrick.com.
What kind of information does terapatrick collect?
-We collect personal information that you provide to us such as your name, e-mail address, street address and telephone number. We generally collect this personal information on our registration and order forms when you sign up to receive products or services from terapatrick.
-When you participate in Site contests and polls, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail, username and password. We may also collect information from our online surveys if you choose to participate, such as age, gender, education and income level.
-When you visit terapatrick, we collect certain anonymous demographic information about you, including your IP address, zip code and browser program. We also collect information regarding your use of the Site through the use of cookies.
-If you choose to post messages, comments or other information in one of the public forums on the Site, information about you as you choose to disclose in your posting will become public information and archived on our servers.
-If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We will maintain a record or notes of communications with you regarding your account.
How does terapatrick use your information?
-terapatrick uses your information in order to process your credit card payments, to fulfill your orders and/or requests, to assist your viewing of terapatrick, to communicate with you, and to provide you with information about terapatrick, some of our partners and third party companies in which we feel you may be interested. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and Site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally.
-terapatrick uses your e-mail address to contact you when necessary and to send periodic e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mails to you about services and products offered by us as well as by third party companies in which we think you may be interested.
-We use IP addresses and anonymous demographic information to tailor your experiences at terapatrick by showing content in which we think you will be interested and displaying content according to your preferences. Anonymous demographic information is shared with advertisers and market researchers on an aggregate basis.
-We use information collected to evaluate and improve our services. We may develop and use, in our sole discretion, consumer research, which may be based on your use of our services.
-Personal information collected on and/or through the Site is stored and processed in the United States and by using the Site; you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country to the United States.
Does terapatrick share information with 3rd party sites?
-In some cases, we will share information we collect (including personal information and/or anonymous demographic information) with third party companies who may offer products or services in which we believe you may be interested. We also share this information with third parties with whom we partner to co-promote and administer contests on terapatrick.
-We may also share information we collect with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the services we provide, such as maintaining our servers and processing or fulfilling orders for products and services you purchase through terapatrick.
-We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so by law, court order or governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of terapatrick, another user or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.
-In the event of a change in ownership or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all user information collected in connection with the Sites, including but not limited to email addresses, to a separate entity. terapatrick will notify you (via a posting on the Sites or the Policy or via email (in our discretion) of such a transfer, and you may choose to modify your registration information at that time. This means that if you are concerned about your personal data migrating to a new owner, you can cancel and deactivate your account by emailing: support@darkreachcash.com
Do we use cookies?
-Yes. Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored on your computer for future access. The Sites use cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making it easier for you to navigate through our Sites or to make a feature work better. Generally, cookies can be disabled at your discretion. However, you must accept cookies in order to navigate the Site, register or purchase photo and/or video Content.
Refund Policy
Refunds for purchases or recurring charges may be requested by contacting customer support. Refunds or credits will not be issued for partially used Memberships. The decision to refund a charge does not imply the obligation to issue additional future refunds. Should a refund be issued by terapatrick for any reason, it will be credited solely to the payment method used in the original transaction. terapatrick.com will not issue refunds by cash, check, or to another payment mechanism.
terapatrick.com will make every effort to make sure that photo and/or video Content is in working order before uploading and releasing Content on the Site for sale. In the event that a file is corrupt or defective, please contact customer support by emailing support@darkreachcash.com. We will contact you within 24-48 hours with a resolution to your problem.
Billing issues do arise and we understand this, if you feel there has been a billing error, please do not hesitate to contact terapatrick customer support by emailing; support@darkreachcash.com or contact our Authorized Sales Agents SegPay.com and Epoch.com.
Join My Site for Instant Access Right Now
My site has all of my archived videos and DVD movies for the past 15 years! Full downloads and video streaming too!
Subscribe to our monthly newsletter and be!
Copyright © 2020 Tera Patrick. All Rights reserved. Privacy Policy | Terms | Contact: support@darkreachcash.com
CHARGES WILL APPEAR AS SEGPAY.COM*ANDOMARK.COM or EPOCH.com Our Authorized Billers
18 U.S.C. 2257 Record-Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement | Billed by Andomark, LLC 24307 Magic Mtn Pkwy #435, Valencia, CA 91355
